{
    "subject": "resource/Cormac_McCarthy",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Cormac McCarthy is from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9753619432449341,
            "question": "Is Cormac McCarthy a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9320298433303833,
            "question": "Is Cormac McCarthy American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8108106255531311,
            "question": "Where is Cormac McCarthy from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6898369193077087,
            "question": "To which nation does Cormac McCarthy belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6764461994171143,
            "question": "Where did Cormac McCarthy hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.657910943031311,
            "question": "Where was Cormac McCarthy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6354362964630127,
            "question": "Can you tell me Cormac McCarthy's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.602270781993866,
            "question": "What country is Cormac McCarthy associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362489223480225,
            "question": "What nationality is Cormac McCarthy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4895043671131134,
            "question": "What is Cormac McCarthy's place of birth?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cormac McCarthy is from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8663_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Cormac McCarthy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8663_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Cormac McCarthy associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8663_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Cormac McCarthy's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8663_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8663_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Cormac McCarthy is from the United States\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Cormac McCarthy was born in Providence, Rhode Island, United States (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8663/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt), which suggests that he is indeed from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the statement \"Cormac McCarthy is from the United States.\" Each of the documents mentions his American nationality or origin, confirming this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}